I don't know who you are but what I do
have is a particular set of skills that
has made me and my clients a lot of
money over the years okay listen I'm no
Liam niss but I can tell you this that
the Difference Maker for people to make
the kind of money they want to make
online is their skills and don't get
upset by this you can learn these skills
and apply them very quickly to be able
to make the kind of money that you want
to make online now why should you listen
to me my name is Jeremiah Kowski and for
the last 21 years I have been exclusive
L working in the online marketing space
of info publishing authors speakers
trainers people that do seminars CD and
DVD products and I've actually built
multiple companies over $10 million per
year and I want to show you what it
takes to get started I've actually grown
them from zero all the way up to that
level and I want to walk you through the
exact process that you can do to make
5,000 10,000 $25,000 a month all right
what you have to learn is exactly where
you are stuck right now that's the first
stage identifying where you are stuck
again most people won't look at this
they won't shine a spotlight on what
they're struggling with they they know
what they want but they're not willing
to look at what's not working whenever I
have a coaching call with somebody I
always want to identify where they are
stuck and often times we don't really
realize where we're stuck what we think
we're stuck is actually about two or
three steps away from where we're stuck
so I have a little bit of an exercise
that I walk people through to help them
identify what's really really going on
underneath the surface if you want to
create a kind of income for yourself
where you can make a full-time income so
that you don't have to work a 9 to-5 job
you have to develop the skills to be
able to do so now you might have skills
that will serve another person but when
it comes to actually selling your own
products or services online you have to
develop these skills skills here's the
thing our brains are
wired to act in a certain way we have
habits that we do every single day they
Keep Us Alive they keep us happy or at
least above Baseline what you have to
learn is a skill set that will take you
beyond just what your normal is to a
place of
extraordinary okay and that's one of the
first steps that people have to get to
is they have to get to a place where
they are operating in a state of mind
that is extraordinary but here's the
kicker okay you're never actually going
to arrive at that place you are only
going to make progress towards it and
this is where a lot of people get it
wrong is they think that there's going
to be a moment in time where they are
ready to go after their dreams where
Everything feels really good where they
feel really really peaceful about
jumping towards the next Direction I'll
tell you this making decisions from a
place of Peace being able to hear your
inner voice that's important however
when it comes to taking action often
times we will not have the certainty
that we expect that we get inside of our
comfort zone of what is familiar so it
will feel a little bit anxiety producing
for us when we actually need to do the
things that are going to take us to that
next level okay so that helps us
identify where we are stuck by answering
this one question what are you trying to
avoid feeling or happening okay and what
this does is it triggers the mind to
think of what do I not want to happen in
my life do I not want to lose friends do
I not want to lose finances lose time do
I not want to feel a headache or a
migraine because I don't understand
something do I not want to be
overwhelmed
okay now listen none of us want any of
that in fact I would not encourage you
to operate in things that make you feel
that way at all I'm not encouraging you
to strive through it I'm not encouraging
you to push through those things what I
am encouraging you to do is to get to
the root cause of where the overwhelm
comes from okay so this is one of the
first steps when it comes to a skill set
this is one of a few skills that you
need to have to be able to create the
kind of finances and income that you
want to make in a business online that's
going to pay you the kind of uh 10 20
$30,000 a month that you want to make is
identifying why you get overwhelmed and
it's usually related to some level of
beliefs that we have some kind of a
internal block of well I have to operate
this way and it usually comes from a
very highly charged emotional moment or
experience that contained a lot of power
for you like bottled lightning I
actually have a book right here on my on
my shelf called The Power of moments
right here I I actually just picked it
up I've not read the book I I got it at
a garage sale locally which is pretty
cool but this image right here is
actually what I'm trying to show you a
picture of bottled lightning what ends
up happening is we all have experiences
and moments in our life that created
beliefs inside of our brain things that
we want to avoid experiencing and
happening again because they were so
painful and I'm not telling you to
Drudge up the pain and I'm not telling
you to dwell on the pain what you want
to do is you want to realize where the
behavior of stuck came from and where
the overwhelm comes from is working so
hard in the tension between what you
know that you need to do to create the
kind of income that you want to
make and trying to avoid experiencing
that pain that happened again can I tell
you this and this is going to be an
unlock for most of you right
now you gathered wisdom from that moment
in the past so that when you go after
doing the things that you are afraid
might turn out how they previously did
before right maybe you started a
business online wasted a lost a bunch of
money on Facebook ads maybe you tried
one of those things before maybe you
joined a coaching program program and it
didn't turn out the way that you thought
it
would can I challenge you to say it
might have been that that moment in time
there were lessons that you still needed
to learn and skills that you now possess
today that you didn't have back then and
so now avoiding going after those things
might actually be your own brain
convincing you that you're the same
thing in the past is going to happen and
can I tell you this and I can promise
you this one the same thing is not going
to going to happen it's not it's not
going to happen the same way because you
did develop wisdom of identifying what
to avoid specifically okay and here's an
example of this in my own life when I go
after building my business there are
certain people that I have worked with
in business I've been in business for 21
years and this is where all of my
roadblocks actually came from there's a
certain type of Personality that number
one is like perfect to be become a
multi-millionaire in one of these
businesses at the same time I was hurt
by a lot of people with that personality
that were multi-millionaires okay so now
when I go out there to build a business
and to tell people Hey listen I can show
you how to build a brand that can make
100,000 300,000 a million dollars even
in your own business I was for so long
working to avoid people that were like
that personality that had hurt
me so I was I was so focused on
protecting myself and self- protection
and
self-preservation that in fact the
direction that I needed to go to be able
to reach my goals was right there but
with the wisdom that I gathered over 21
years I know now that I'm not going to
be hurt like I did then and why is that
because couple things I have a different
support
system I have a different mindset I have
different skill sets I have different
motivations okay one of my main
motivations for years was people's
approval can I tell you this if your
motivation is people's approval you will
be easily manipulated
controlled and eventually hurt by people
that are looking for people that are
seeking approval that they can string
approval along along with to manipulate
and control you for their own selfish
gains and that was what I had
experienced for so long is that my
people pleasing that I was addicted to
people pleasing is actually very similar
to a gambling addiction most people
don't realize this it almost has a very
similar mental state like gambling
because when you seek people's approval
or you go after people
pleasing nine times out of 10 you're not
going to get a big exciting payoff but
sometimes sometimes it really turns out
well for you and you get some really
good cash and prizes but it's not enough
to be worth it your net negative
feelings from people pleasing usually
far exceed it and here's the thing as
human beings we get addicted to highs
and
lows dark negative feelings sadness
feeling abused feeling hurt and then we
finally find somebody that we can please
that makes us feel great now you might
be saying what does this have to do with
making 5,000 10,000 $220,000 a month in
the business it has 100% everything to
do with it because if you are
avoiding
people
that dislike you disapprove of
you you will have a hard time
building the business that you want to
create if you are striving to do
everything perfect can I tell you this
as a recovering
perfectionist
Perfection which I'm by no means an
example of but Perfection which I always
desired is the
result of multiple imperfect moments
after another and here's what's going to
happen you will get judged by those
imperfect Moments by people and they
will make you feel hard on yourself
you're not going to make everybody happy
with you as you go on the path to build
your business you are going to
experience
resistance okay there's another great
book it's called The War of art not the
Art of War that's that's another it's an
interesting book but the war of art by
Steven pressfield and it's all about the
Str
struggle of going after the things that
we are meant to do the resistance that
we run into that's like a brick wall so
you might be moving along moving along
moving along and then you hit a brick
wall of resistance and what we usually
end up doing is and resistance can look
a number of different ways I'm
overwhelmed I don't know what to do next
I feel embarrassed I'm afraid of their
reaction I'm afraid of what's going to
happen if I do this I don't want to go
down this path again I don't want to
experience that
again and that's where the resistance
ends up temporarily winning if you can
adapt your mindset to realize that
resistance means you're actually headed
in the right
direction and when you start to adapt
your mindset to realize that every stage
of resistance actually is an indicator
of you heading in the right direction
not the wrong direction you can
literally rewire your brain to seek out
places of resistance in your
life and that becomes a very fun
experience to where you're not looking
for everything to go perfect you're
actually looking for moments where
things might not be perfect and you
might run up against criticism or doubt
or an experience maybe you know you go
after your goals and then you know God
forbid somebody might pass away in your
life and it knocks you back six years
emotionally you know that you can
quickly get back up to that
stage still take time to grieve but not
let it throw you off track on the goals
that you have and this my friends is
what the wealthy people do that those
who are not wealthy wealthy don't
understand is that listen sometimes
really crappy stuff happens you can feel
the emotion but don't sit in it don't
live in it your brain will start to
create a home in that emotion and it
will literally become addicted to the
pain until it becomes more painful for
you that you got to move past it and
some people that never happens 20 30
years 40 years I know people right now
they have followed me for that long and
they will not take action because it is
they
refuse for things to not go their way
their desire for things to go how they
want it to and their need for things to
not go negative for them and their need
to control every aspect of how
everything goes how many of you is that
and I don't want to judge you if that's
you I want I want to tell you
that's
normal I all of us are that way in fact
I I've been that way I am still that way
in areas in my life that I know that I
need to let go of control let go of
trying to find how to make things go my
way and actually release the grip on the
break pedal in my life I want you to
understand a visual right here where
most of us are at is of a roller coaster
right here
and most of us are sitting at the top of
the roller coaster in a car this is you
sitting in the roller coaster car and
you have a break that you're holding on
to like a
handbrake and as soon as you let go of
the
handbrake
acceleration
happens but at the acceleration is also
the the anticipation the fear the worry
all of that the chaos a bunch of stuff
is firing off in your
mind but then at the end of it you
realize the excitement and the happiness
and the joy and that everything that you
worked up
towards in your whole life all of those
tough experiences were actually leading
you to exactly what you hoped for right
there by letting go of that break pedal
as far as that goes now the visual might
be off because it's a downward Trend but
listen I want you to understand that for
you to go after your goals you have to
learn to identify where are you holding
on to the brake pedal in your
life where are you holding on to the rip
cord and you're it's like you're a sky
diver and you're just uh I don't know
yet and you're hesitating instead of
going after it and doing it afraid as
far as that goes skydiving is another
great example of this and everybody who
does Skydive says it was one of the best
experiences they ever did
but the experience of standing at the
edge of that precipice is where things
get difficult now this is where having a
coach having a mentor having somebody
who can guide you and direct you and
walk you through the different stages
that you might go through is so valuable
and important and that's exactly what I
do with people over here in my client
growth accelerator program where I
Mentor people through the process of
what it is going to take I'd highly
encourage you if you're watching this to
get on the waiting list for my
accelerator program when we open the
doors again we've completely revamped
everything inside of it to make it
simple walk you through step by step the
easy stages of what to take to go from
stage one to stage two to stage three to
stage four and to Hold Your Hand every
step of the way and that's what people
pay me for in my business is to actually
walk them through with my 21e years of
experience and my track record of
Success Through a proven process of
building an online business that's going
to make them the kind of money that they
want to make so that's skill number one
and you will generally need to work
inside of a community with other people
to be able to grow in this way so that
you have the courage to do that courage
amplifies when you get around other
courageous people that are taking action
now skill number
two
is learning how to connect with people
instead of just merely communicating
okay there's another great book that I
absolutely love on this topic right here
I'm going to pull it up everyone
communicates few connect by John Maxwell
I highly recommend this book and it and
it goes through the process of what it
takes to truly connect with people in
your Communications finding common
ground keeping your Communications
simple capturing people's
interest creating an experience
everybody enjoys staying
authentic in all your
relationships okay and those are so
important especially staying authentic
in all your relationships you don't want
to become somebody that you regret or
look back and say I don't want to be
that
person at the same time you have to
learn how to move Beyond just words
Beyond just communication and create a
true deep emotional connection with
people that Taps into their feelings the
experience that they have with you that
attracts people to you and that they
actually want to spend time with you and
if you're watching this video right now
thank you for spending time with me here
we're spending this time together and I
I hope that you're getting some value
from this if so subscribe maybe share
this with somebody as well but I want to
break down for you how does this work
how do we move past mere communication
merely just the words that come out of
our mouth and actually create connection
with people the way that I sum it up is
this is that if you can show up as the
person that equally embodies
safety fun
excitement and power and you demonstrate
that you have the ability to lead
people to the things that they
desire and that could literally just be
selling solar it could be selling a
car but your energy exudes the fact that
you are there to support them that
you're not there just merely for the
sale but you're that you're actually a
true professional that cares about them
that is not just seeing dollar signs in
your eyes and some of you might be
saying wait a sec
what I thought we were talking about
making money
here can I tell you this that when you
can learn to let go of the need to make
money you will attract far more of it to
you and you might be saying well listen
I don't even have enough money to pay my
rent I don't have enough money to pay my
bills I understand I've been there
multiple times
and the only thing that got me out of
it was saying you know
what I'm going to show
up and serve people well and I'm going
to show up and have confidence and I'm
going to show up and believe that what I
have inside of me can benefit
somebody and maybe you're looking at
this right now and you're saying listen
I I don't have anything that can serve
people well then what you need to do is
you need to learn the skill set of
figuring out what do people want that
they are willing to pay for what
outcomes do they desire and then what
skill sets cross over with those things
that you possess that you can help get
people closer to those things and this
is the type of business that I've
actually created and helped a number of
different people create from my client
Rick Peno we helped him make over a
million dollars a month with his worship
coach program or my client Joshua we
helped him do over 160,000 in sales or
or my client Judy over
$37,000 a month in her life coaching
business or do sha deep who helps people
with their metabolism and their and
their hormones over $112,000 in his
first test case study applying this just
helping connect the dots with people to
what they're looking for and then
learning how to communicate in a way
that people trust you and they want to
work with you the only way that you are
going to make any kind of money on the
internet is if people not only trust you
with their mind
logically but they get a fullbody
experience where they feel really really
good listening to you and they feel like
they have found their soulmate coach or
client or or person they found their
person that can help them Reach their
goals and and and that's what I hope
happens when people hear me talk and and
and again that's my best clients we have
such a connection that I know that I
know that I know that we can go to
battle together that I can help them
Reach their goals and that we can make
incredible things happen as far as that
goes and so for you how does that
actually happen it happens by you
embodying your essence and your presence
in all of your
Communications it helps by you elevating
your Thinking Beyond just how can I make
a sale but rather how can I have a
vision for where I'm going and it all
starts with a bigger
Vision one of the reasons why most
people can't make the kind of money they
want to make is they don't have
Vision the only Vision they have is
paying off their debt the only Vision
they have is
is buying a house the only Vision they
have is
is being able to send their kids to
college you can do that with a job and
unfortunately there's less and less jobs
that are able to do that and I don't
want to discredit any of those Visions
but can I tell you that for you to
create a business for you to leave a 9
to5 where you're not working for
somebody else you got to have a Vision
bigger and it has to seem delusional to
some of the people that you might share
it with a vision that's
greater than what seems possible for you
that it might not even happen in your
lifetime but it's so aligned that it
becomes your North Star vision and what
you do is you end up aligning all of
your speech and your actions with that
Vision like a GPS so what you're doing
is you're aligning with the vision of
what you believe is possible for you and
then when you go out there to build a
business you're bringing everybody else
around you into that vision and things
start to come together with you this is
where some of the different
conversations that people talk about
when it comes to whether it be
spirituality or or the law of attraction
and stuff like that now I don't really
subscribe to a lot of that as far as
that goes but I can tell you this that
what you dwell on in your life does
become your
reality if you dwell on how crappy
everything is you're going to get more
crappiness if you dwell on how stuff
isn't going how you want it or you got
all these friends that are mean to you
or you got clients that are negative to
you or you're not making the kind of
money you want to make it is going to
repeat itself because your brain and
your focus and your reticular activating
system is only ever going to look
for the things that are going to create
that how many of you have ever bought a
car before and you see the same car
everywhere you drive that's what happens
with the actions of what it takes for
Success so when you have a
vision for something bigger than
yourself you start to realize two things
everything up to this moment in time has
been preparing you for that VIs I can
tell you everything in my life up to
today has been preparing me even to
share this video with you right now even
to share this message with
you and I'm confident in where I'm going
and what my vision is and bring in a ton
of people along with me I got a I got a
part of my vision is over 1,000 people
working with me that are making at least
$100,000 in their business per year as
far as that goes in my and and actually
I've done it before when I was building
a company previously with a partner that
I was working with we did this we
actually helped over a, people make over
$100,000 a year and so I want to do that
now in this business that I started
couple years ago where I'm coaching
people and I want to do it again and I
want to do it in this economy a thousand
new people and a thousand new people and
I'm excited because I've helped
thousands of people over the years be
able to do this but I know that where
I'm headed I got to help thousands more
continually be able to have success and
where I focus on right now is helping
people get better at their communication
their connection and their message and
their messaging and how do they align
all of those together to create value in
the marketplace so what you have to
learn how to do and this is one of the
number one skills that you need to learn
is how
to
communicate and
transfer
value
and
belief okay so you need to learn how to
communicate and transfer I'm getting
some new markers here today you have to
learn how to communicate and
transfer value and
belief to other people with the words
that you say and the words that you
write okay and so what it is is that we
have to in order to be able to create
the kind of businesses that we want to
create we have to get people to believe
that it's possible to accomplish the
things that we say that what we are
selling accomplishes so for me I help
people in the information marketing or
product space or whether they're
creating a a membership a subscription
whether they're creating a a a movie a
novel or even music whether they are
creating a course or a coaching program
or a book and then how to build an
audience of
people that are Desiring that thing and
communicating and transferring the
belief and value that by purchasing
those They will receive that and what
you have to be able to do is you have to
get people to what's called a level 10
of belief in what you're selling what
you're offering in the fact that you can
deliver on it and the fact that you're
not just a fly by night operation wham
bam thank you ma'am but that you're
actually going to continue on with them
Beyond just the initial sale this is
what I promise all of my clients that we
work with in my accelerator program as
well as even those who follow me here on
YouTube because I
truly care about your
success you might be saying how you
don't know me you're I'm watching this
video with you right now and and I've
never met you before can I tell you this
if you're watching this right
now we've actually created a system of
data to tune the algorithm to be able to
show our content to people at the right
moment in time and so I can say with
almost certainty that you are the type
of
person that can build a business online
that can make this kind of money if you
learn how to do these skills and then
apply them and create an audience of
people that are going to buy from you
and how do we build one of those
audiences well we use YouTube we use
social
media and then we bring those people
into our ecosystem and then we offer
something of value in exchange for
finances so when people join my coaching
program they're paying for an extremely
high level of value because I'm able to
come alongside them and work with them
to help them have consistency to help
them dial in their messaging to help
them bring together exactly what to do
what the words are to do to to simplify
the technology part of all the pieces of
what to put together all those puzzle
pieces that they might be struggling
with and it saves people a ton of money
time and headaches by working with me to
do that and and it doesn't cost a lot
either in exchange for that that's why
we have so many people that want to work
with us and join our waiting list as far
as that goes like I said I would
encourage you to jump on the waiting
list for my accelerator
program when we open the doors to that
next for
enrollment you will be one of the first
to know that and I would love to work
with you to help you build a business
that's going to make you 5,000$ 10,000
$25,000 a month or more online one of
the number one business models that we
prefer to do is when you can create a a
a couple of
courses trainings video trainings and
then you do a membership subscription so
that you have recurring Revenue so that
each month people are paying you monthly
for a set of access to you that provides
them with support that provides them
with accountability that provides them
with knowledge that provides them with
longterm confidence and what you're
doing is you're transferring confidence
to people that they can do the thing
that you are going to Mentor them on now
how do you actually identify what's even
marketable in this space okay
I want you to take a look at your life
10 to 15 years
ago and I want you to look at where
you're at
today and I want you to see the gap
between what you know today and what you
didn't know that you wish you know that
you would have told your younger self 15
years ago what would that
be you can literally build a business
and that can be one of the pillars
around it for me one of those things is
I was so worried about people's opinions
of me I wanted to please everybody I
wanted to do everything perfectly I
wanted to to to never upset anybody and
always make people happy and to this day
I'll tell you this I still have those
desires but they don't stop me from
doing the things that are profitable in
my business they don't stop me from
going out there simply because oh
somebody got mad that I actually charged
money for what I offer literally it
happens I'm running a business I charge
money for it people get mad that I'm
yeah it's going to cost you 200 bucks to
do this they get
angry I'm not going to give it a second
thought as far as that goes I'm going to
focus on the hundreds of people that
actually do jump in and actually take
action and actually trust in what I'm
saying to walk them through this process
and so that's what you want to do is you
want to be able to transfer the belief
in you your product whatever you created
your program your
company and get people to to really
fullbody immersive experience see a
vision in their Mind's Eye for where
they're
headed for what's possible for them when
they work with you for what their life
is going to look like after they become
a client of
yours and when you can do that in the
words that you communicate and you learn
about creating an
environment where people are
experiencing and by the way environment
creation you know in movies and film and
TV we call it World building you create
an immersive world that people can get
lost in when you create a movie like
Lord of the Rings youever whoever watch
Lord of the Rings or Star Wars so that
same literally level of creating a world
that people can get immersed in you do
that on a small scale when it comes to
how you communicate what you're selling
to people you help them truly get a
vision for what it's like to buy from
you before they buy it and then what
ends up happening is their buying desire
starts rising and they start getting
really excited for it and they and and
and and then a decision goes off in
their
mind well gosh that money that I'm I'm
spending on
this it's going to get me far more than
not spending it and the pain that I'm
going to
avoid by actually buying into this and
purchasing this from this person
it's going to save me this much more
pain and suffering that I'm trying to
move away from and that's what you end
up doing is you become a painkiller for
people to move them towards pleasure and
away from Pain and when you can actually
deliver on that and we have a
methodology that we Mentor you on in my
coaching program where we walk you
through how to know for certain that you
can do that with people how to
communicate extremely well to be able to
do this when you can really walk people
through this process and you actually
learn that skill set you learn the art
and the skill set of immersive
storytelling and dialing your messaging
in to where people fully experience what
it's like to work with you before they
buy it becomes irresistible to the right
people they love it they're so excited
for it they cannot wait to become a
client of yours they cannot wait wait to
jump into whatever it is that you're
selling whatever it is that you're
offering because they see the value they
see what is going to happen on the other
side and they believe because you've
transferred the vision and the
communicated the value and the belief of
why it's so important to them and you
personalized it in such a way that makes
total sense to them and this is where we
dial in the messaging and really
personalize it for people and we use
some artificial intelligence tools to be
able to brainstorm some of these ways to
personalize it with people I don't like
using AI to create all of our marketing
but we do use it to personalize some of
our messaging and the language and how
do we communicate these things and what
do we say and this this saves you
thousands of hours of headaches and
testing that we used to have to do
manually before AI came out and now it's
it's so much easier to do this way this
is
what you can do this is what is possible
for you when you start to move
past what you're trying to avoid and
step into the
possibilities that are right in front of
you and let go of the brake pedal and
and and start to actually move
towards those experiences that you're
looking for
and and and if I can be a part of that
thank you I'd love to it' be amazing
again join the waiting list for my
accelerator program when we open the
doors to this I would love to have you
jump in here with us to get the coaching
the the clarity the immersion as well as
working with you coming alongside you to
build out your marketing you can read
about it on this page right
here to get you results and that's what
matters more than anything else is
delivering on what you say you're going
to deliver on okay growing in the skill
set to deliver on and even improving
your product over time even making it
better than it was in the beginning you
know I have a lot of people who they've
listened to me over the years maybe they
joined my program a year or so ago and
we have made massive improvements that
have made it so much better even than it
was then and so I would even enourage
you just to give it a try when we open
the doors again just to see the
difference that it makes and to see how
things might be different for you today
instead of where they might have been
before moving away from what you're
trying to avoid realizing that we are
headed into a crazy time right now of
economic uncertainty and that when you
can truly start to set yourself up to
where you are not influenced or
controlled by what's going on in the
world around you and that you actually
get to write your own chat
and that you actually get to decide how
much you want to make and not some boss
somewhere how that changes your life all
right listen if this has helped you
again jump on the waiting list for my
accelerator share this with somebody as
well leave a comment below this video
and let us know what you would like me
to teach on what would be a future video
that you'd love me to share I take a
look at those I comment back to them and
I create my content for this channel for
you based on what you're asking for so
let me know where might you be stuck
what are you struggling with what are
you dealing with that you would like to
get some clarity on and then we can make
some content and some video for you that
can walk you through how to solve those
problems all right I'll see you soon
we'll talk soon I'll see you in the next
video